跟帮派没有关系是吗
at the bus stop was not gang affiliated?
是的  长官  保罗·霍勒  高四学生
That is correct, sir. Paul Haller, high school senior.
但也不是什么好鸟
Not an angel, though.
霍勒曾因几次小偷小摸被逮捕过
Haller has a few minor robbery arrests from the past,
警方在他身上发现了一个钱包
and police found a wallet on his body,
现金和信用卡都属于一个叫西塔·帕特尔的人
cash and credit cards belonging to a Sita Patel.
抢钱包
Purse-snatching?
黑帮分子  抢劫犯
Gang members, mugger.
这可能是义务警员所为
We might be looking at a vigilante.
我刚跟克利夫兰警方通过电话
All right, I just got off the phone with Cleveland P.D.
如果我们面对的是杀人狂
If we are dealing with a spree killer,
至少他现在还能自控
at least he's on a slower boil now.
过去几个小时没有犯下新的案子
No new incidents reported in the past hour.
加油站的死者不仅中了枪
The victim at the gas station wasn't just shot.
尸体表明他被一辆大车
The body showed signs of having been run over multiple times